this is what
this
we used to
is
what
we
used
to
call the
call
genomic revolution
the
genomic
revolution
And it was
And
a very difficult
it
was
a
very
difficult
space though the
space
though
the
innovation was
innovation
taking place
was
taking
place
The investment markets
The
were not interested
investment
markets
were
not
interested
in it for
in
a of One
lots of necessary
lots
therefore not
of
necessary
therefore
not
very high
very
if any
high
if
any
cash flows
cash
flows
And the cash
And
cushions needed
the
cash
cushions
needed
to be built
to
up We think
be
built
up
We
think
they've done a
they've
lot in the
done
a
lot
in
the
last few years
last
to become more
few
years
to
become
more
efficient And so
efficient
we're beginning to
And
so
we're
beginning
to
see outperformance from
see
that space as
outperformance
from
that
space
as
well because now
well
many people are
because
now
many
people
are
beginning to
beginning
we're seeing cures
to
we're
seeing
cures
to disease We're
to
seeing early diagnosis
disease
We're
seeing
early
diagnosis
thanks to AI
thanks
and sequencing technologies
to
AI
and
sequencing
technologies